<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>alumni | Electrical Instrumentation at UST</title>
    <link>/tag/alumni/</link>
      <atom:link href="/tag/alumni/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>alumni</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hub67c49e2d9e3d1fe433c419f415a9895_280832_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>alumni</title>
      <link>/tag/alumni/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Schewe</title>
      <link>/people/matthew_schewe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/people/matthew_schewe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Matthew was a UST Electrical Engineering Major who graduated in the Spring of 2020. He worked on electronics for a new ion-channel amplifier. He is a multisim expert and finished an entire PCB design cycle in the summer of 2019.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mohamed Abdalla</title>
      <link>/people/mohamed_abdalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/people/mohamed_abdalla/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mohamed is a UST Master&amp;rsquo;s student in the graduate programs in software. He is working on an independent study project to develop inexpensive methods to calibrate and evaluate accelerometers and gyroscopes (IMUs).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Jans</title>
      <link>/people/ryan_jans/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/people/ryan_jans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ryan graduated from UST with an Electrical Engineering Major in the spring of 2020. He did excellent work on optical time-of-flight depth sensors and was the first undergraduate to be the first author on a reviewed journal paper in our lab &lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/8982043&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Characterization of a Miniaturized IR Depth Sensor With a Programmable Region-of-Interest That Enables Hazard Mapping Applications&lt;/a&gt;. He also worked on an industry linked RF communications project. Ryan is now a graduate student at the Air Force Institute of Technology in Ohio.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phillip Kuplic</title>
      <link>/people/phillip_kuplic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/people/phillip_kuplic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Phil is a UST Mechanical Engineering Major who graduated in the Spring of 2020. He constructed an apparatus for characterizing LED illumination systems for microscope and spectrophotometer applications. He presented his work on LED characterization at the APS March meeting in Boston in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Savannah Johnson</title>
      <link>/people/savannah_johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/people/savannah_johnson/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Savannah graduated in the Spring of 2020 with a major in Mechanical Engineering and minors in Electrical Engineering and Aerospace Studies. Along the way she won &lt;a href=&#34;https://news.stthomas.edu/rotc-cadet-savannah-johnson-receives-three-national-awards/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;3 national awards as a ROTC cadet&lt;/a&gt;
She is curious about the real-world applications of physics and mathematics. Electronics, control systems, automation, and transportation systems spark her interest.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lucas Manke</title>
      <link>/people/lucas_manke/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/people/lucas_manke/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lucas graduated in the Spring of 2020 and was a senior majoring in Mechanical Engineering and pursuing minors in Business Administration and Military Science.  He was a member of the varsity swim team at UST and a cadet in Army ROTC at the University of Minnesota.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xiaokang Li</title>
      <link>/people/xiaokang_li/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/people/xiaokang_li/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Xiaokang completed an electrical engineering Master&amp;rsquo;s degree at the University of St. Thomas.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
